[
  {
    "question_no.": 1,
    "Question": "Which global brand is famous for its 'Just Do It' slogan and a swoosh logo?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Nike",
    "Option3": "Puma",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 2,
    "Question": "What company is known for its iconic golden arches and the slogan 'I'm Lovin' It'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "McDonald's",
    "Option4": "KFC",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 3,
    "Question": "The multinational technology company with a bitten apple logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Apple",
    "Option4": "Google",
    "Answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 4,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its red and white logo and is often associated with the holiday season?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Dr Pepper",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 5,
    "Question": "What is the primary product of the brand Levi's?",
    "Option1": "Sneakers",
    "Option2": "Watches",
    "Option3": "Jeans",
    "Option4": "T-shirts",
    "Answer": "Jeans"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 6,
    "Question": "The brand known for its home furniture and meatballs is:",
    "Option1": "Walmart",
    "Option2": "Target",
    "Option3": "IKEA",
    "Option4": "The Home Depot",
    "Answer": "IKEA"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 7,
    "Question": "Which luxury car brand has a four-ring logo?",
    "Option1": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option2": "BMW",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Lexus",
    "Answer": "Audi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 8,
    "Question": "The brand associated with the slogan 'The Ultimate Driving Machine' is:",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Audi",
    "Option3": "Toyota",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "BMW"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 9,
    "Question": "What is the name of the multinational technology company famous for its search engine?",
    "Option1": "Apple",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Google",
    "Option4": "Amazon",
    "Answer": "Google"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 10,
    "Question": "Which coffee brand is known for its green and white siren logo?",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 11,
    "Question": "The multinational corporation that owns brands like Gillette, Pampers, and Tide is:",
    "Option1": "Unilever",
    "Option2": "Procter & Gamble",
    "Option3": "Johnson & Johnson",
    "Option4": "Nestlé",
    "Answer": "Procter & Gamble"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 12,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of sports drink known for its lightning bolt logo?",
    "Option1": "Powerade",
    "Option2": "Gatorade",
    "Option3": "Monster Energy",
    "Option4": "Red Bull",
    "Answer": "Gatorade"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 13,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its yellow and red shell logo?",
    "Option1": "BP",
    "Option2": "Chevron",
    "Option3": "Shell",
    "Option4": "ExxonMobil",
    "Answer": "Shell"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 14,
    "Question": "The clothing and accessories brand with a polo player on a horse as its logo is:",
    "Option1": "Tommy Hilfiger",
    "Option2": "Ralph Lauren",
    "Option3": "Calvin Klein",
    "Option4": "Lacoste",
    "Answer": "Ralph Lauren"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 15,
    "Question": "What company is known for its colorful interlocking plastic bricks?",
    "Option1": "Mattel",
    "Option2": "Hasbro",
    "Option3": "LEGO",
    "Option4": "Fisher-Price",
    "Answer": "LEGO"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 16,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the PlayStation gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Nintendo",
    "Option3": "Sony",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Sony"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 17,
    "Question": "Which car company has a star-shaped logo and is headquartered in Germany?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Mercedes-Benz"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 18,
    "Question": "What brand of chocolate is known for its triangular shape and name?",
    "Option1": "Cadbury",
    "Option2": "Hershey's",
    "Option3": "Toblerone",
    "Option4": "Lindt",
    "Answer": "Toblerone"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 19,
    "Question": "The clothing company with the iconic 'alligator' or 'crocodile' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Ralph Lauren",
    "Option2": "Lacoste",
    "Option3": "Tommy Hilfiger",
    "Option4": "Gucci",
    "Answer": "Lacoste"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 20,
    "Question": "Which brand's slogan is 'A Diamond is Forever'?",
    "Option1": "Tiffany & Co.",
    "Option2": "Cartier",
    "Option3": "De Beers",
    "Option4": "Harry Winston",
    "Answer": "De Beers"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 21,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its little blue boxes?",
    "Option1": "Cartier",
    "Option2": "Tiffany & Co.",
    "Option3": "Van Cleef & Arpels",
    "Option4": "Bulgari",
    "Answer": "Tiffany & Co."
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 22,
    "Question": "The car company that produces the Corolla and Camry models is:",
    "Option1": "Honda",
    "Option2": "Nissan",
    "Option3": "Toyota",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "Toyota"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 23,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its online marketplace and its Kindle e-readers?",
    "Option1": "eBay",
    "Option2": "Walmart",
    "Option3": "Amazon",
    "Option4": "Alibaba",
    "Answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 24,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the Xbox gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Sony",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Nintendo",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Microsoft"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 25,
    "Question": "What is the name of the popular brand of carbonated soft drink that is a rival of Coca-Cola?",
    "Option1": "Dr Pepper",
    "Option2": "Fanta",
    "Option3": "Sprite",
    "Option4": "Pepsi",
    "Answer": "Pepsi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 26,
    "Question": "The German sports apparel brand with three stripes as its logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Adidas",
    "Option4": "Under Armour",
    "Answer": "Adidas"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 27,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its iconic motorcycle and the slogan 'The world's most valuable motorcycle brand'?",
    "Option1": "Harley-Davidson",
    "Option2": "Kawasaki",
    "Option3": "Yamaha",
    "Option4": "Honda",
    "Answer": "Harley-Davidson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 28,
    "Question": "The brand of watches known for its crown logo is:",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option3": "Rolex",
    "Option4": "TAG Heuer",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 29,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic fragrance 'Chanel No. 5'?",
    "Option1": "Dior",
    "Option2": "Gucci",
    "Option3": "Chanel",
    "Option4": "Hermès",
    "Answer": "Chanel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 30,
    "Question": "The Japanese multinational conglomerate that produces the Walkman and PlayStation is:",
    "Option1": "Panasonic",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "Samsung",
    "Option4": "LG",
    "Answer": "Sony"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 31,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of pizza known for its '30 minutes or it's free' promise?",
    "Option1": "Pizza Hut",
    "Option2": "Domino's Pizza",
    "Option3": "Papa John's",
    "Option4": "Little Caesars",
    "Answer": "Domino's Pizza"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 32,
    "Question": "The car company with a bull logo is:",
    "Option1": "Lamborghini",
    "Option2": "Ferrari",
    "Option3": "Porsche",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "Lamborghini"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 33,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic blue and red flag logo?",
    "Option1": "Calvin Klein",
    "Option2": "Tommy Hilfiger",
    "Option3": "Ralph Lauren",
    "Option4": "Gucci",
    "Answer": "Tommy Hilfiger"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 34,
    "Question": "The multinational food and beverage company that produces Kit Kat and Nescafé is:",
    "Option1": "Kraft Heinz",
    "Option2": "Unilever",
    "Option3": "Nestlé",
    "Option4": "Mars",
    "Answer": "Nestlé"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 35,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its slogan 'Think Different'?",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Google",
    "Option3": "Apple",
    "Option4": "Intel",
    "Answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 36,
    "Question": "The popular online video-sharing platform owned by Google is:",
    "Option1": "Netflix",
    "Option2": "Hulu",
    "Option3": "YouTube",
    "Option4": "TikTok",
    "Answer": "YouTube"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 37,
    "Question": "Which car company has a leaping horse logo?",
    "Option1": "Lamborghini",
    "Option2": "Porsche",
    "Option3": "Ferrari",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "Ferrari"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 38,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the famous Jack Daniel's Tennessee Whiskey is:",
    "Option1": "Jim Beam",
    "Option2": "Johnnie Walker",
    "Option3": "Jack Daniel's",
    "Option4": "Maker's Mark",
    "Answer": "Jack Daniel's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 39,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its iconic denim jackets and 501 jeans?",
    "Option1": "Wrangler",
    "Option2": "Lee",
    "Option3": "Levi's",
    "Option4": "Diesel",
    "Answer": "Levi's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 40,
    "Question": "The multinational beverage company that produces Mountain Dew and 7 Up is:",
    "Option1": "Coca-Cola Company",
    "Option2": "PepsiCo",
    "Option3": "Dr Pepper Snapple Group",
    "Option4": "Nestlé",
    "Answer": "PepsiCo"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 41,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'Because You're Worth It'?",
    "Option1": "Estée Lauder",
    "Option2": "L'Oréal",
    "Option3": "Mary Kay",
    "Option4": "Chanel",
    "Answer": "L'Oréal"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 42,
    "Question": "The brand of home appliances with a red dot logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "LG",
    "Option4": "Dyson",
    "Answer": "Dyson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 43,
    "Question": "What is the brand of fast-food restaurant known for its 'Whopper' sandwich?",
    "Option1": "McDonald's",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "Burger King",
    "Option4": "Taco Bell",
    "Answer": "Burger King"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 44,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the popular Oreo cookie is:",
    "Option1": "Nabisco",
    "Option2": "Keebler",
    "Option3": "General Mills",
    "Option4": "Kraft Heinz",
    "Answer": "Nabisco"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 45,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its iconic trench coats and check pattern?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 46,
    "Question": "The car company with the 'T' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Toyota",
    "Option2": "Tesla",
    "Option3": "Ford",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Tesla"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 47,
    "Question": "What is the brand of luxury watch known for its 'Oyster' case and 'Submariner' model?",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Rolex",
    "Option3": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option4": "Breitling",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 48,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a blue bird as its logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Twitter (now X)",
    "Option4": "LinkedIn",
    "Answer": "Twitter (now X)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 49,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Flying B' logo and luxury cars?",
    "Option1": "Rolls-Royce",
    "Option2": "Bentley",
    "Option3": "Jaguar",
    "Option4": "Aston Martin",
    "Answer": "Bentley"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 50,
    "Question": "What brand of soda is known for its slogan 'The Uncola'?",
    "Option1": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option2": "Pepsi",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Sprite",
    "Answer": "7 Up"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 51,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its red-soled shoes?",
    "Option1": "Jimmy Choo",
    "Option2": "Manolo Blahnik",
    "Option3": "Christian Louboutin",
    "Option4": "Salvatore Ferragamo",
    "Answer": "Christian Louboutin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 52,
    "Question": "The brand of high-end handbags with an iconic 'monogram' pattern is:",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Hermès",
    "Option3": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 53,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its slogan 'Open Happiness'?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "Sprite",
    "Option4": "7 Up",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 54,
    "Question": "The car company that produces the F-150 and Mustang models is:",
    "Option1": "Chevrolet",
    "Option2": "Ford",
    "Option3": "Dodge",
    "Option4": "Toyota",
    "Answer": "Ford"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 55,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its search engine and the 'Don't be evil' motto?",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Apple",
    "Option3": "Google",
    "Option4": "Amazon",
    "Answer": "Google"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 56,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Jumpman' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Adidas",
    "Option3": "Jordan Brand",
    "Option4": "Puma",
    "Answer": "Jordan Brand"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 57,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its iconic 'Swiss Army Knife'?",
    "Option1": "Leatherman",
    "Option2": "Wenger",
    "Option3": "Victorinox",
    "Option4": "Gerber",
    "Answer": "Victorinox"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 58,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a ghost logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Snapchat",
    "Option4": "TikTok",
    "Answer": "Snapchat"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 59,
    "Question": "Which brand of toys is famous for its 'Barbie' doll?",
    "Option1": "Hasbro",
    "Option2": "LEGO",
    "Option3": "Mattel",
    "Option4": "Fisher-Price",
    "Answer": "Mattel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 60,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 61,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of whiskey known for its red label?",
    "Option1": "Jack Daniel's",
    "Option2": "Jim Beam",
    "Option3": "Johnnie Walker",
    "Option4": "Maker's Mark",
    "Answer": "Johnnie Walker"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 62,
    "Question": "The brand of camera known for its iconic 'Eos' series is:",
    "Option1": "Nikon",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "Canon",
    "Option4": "Fujifilm",
    "Answer": "Canon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 63,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'I'm Lovin' It'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 64,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Three-Stripes' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Adidas",
    "Option4": "Under Armour",
    "Answer": "Adidas"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 65,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic 'Check' pattern and trench coats?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 66,
    "Question": "The brand of chocolate known for its triangular shape is:",
    "Option1": "Cadbury",
    "Option2": "Hershey's",
    "Option3": "Toblerone",
    "Option4": "Lindt",
    "Answer": "Toblerone"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 67,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Golden Arches' logo?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "McDonald's",
    "Option4": "KFC",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 68,
    "Question": "The brand of energy drink known for its bull logo is:",
    "Option1": "Monster Energy",
    "Option2": "Red Bull",
    "Option3": "Rockstar",
    "Option4": "NOS Energy Drink",
    "Answer": "Red Bull"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 69,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its 'Just Do It' slogan?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 70,
    "Question": "The brand of luxury car with a four-ring logo is:",
    "Option1": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option2": "BMW",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Lexus",
    "Answer": "Audi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 71,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its 'swoosh' logo?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 72,
    "Question": "The brand of home furnishing known for its flat-pack furniture is:",
    "Option1": "Walmart",
    "Option2": "Target",
    "Option3": "IKEA",
    "Option4": "The Home Depot",
    "Answer": "IKEA"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 73,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of soft drink known for its red and white logo?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Dr Pepper",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 74,
    "Question": "The brand of technology company with a bitten apple logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Apple",
    "Option4": "Google",
    "Answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 75,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'golden arches' and 'Happy Meal'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 76,
    "Question": "The brand of watches known for its crown logo is:",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option3": "Rolex",
    "Option4": "TAG Heuer",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 77,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic fragrance 'Chanel No. 5'?",
    "Option1": "Dior",
    "Option2": "Gucci",
    "Option3": "Chanel",
    "Option4": "Hermès",
    "Answer": "Chanel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 78,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the PlayStation gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Nintendo",
    "Option3": "Sony",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Sony"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 79,
    "Question": "Which car company has a star-shaped logo and is headquartered in Germany?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Mercedes-Benz"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 80,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its online marketplace and its Kindle e-readers?",
    "Option1": "eBay",
    "Option2": "Walmart",
    "Option3": "Amazon",
    "Option4": "Alibaba",
    "Answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 81,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the Xbox gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Sony",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Nintendo",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Microsoft"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 82,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its slogan 'The Ultimate Driving Machine'?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Audi",
    "Option3": "Toyota",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "BMW"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 83,
    "Question": "The brand of sports drink known for its lightning bolt logo is:",
    "Option1": "Powerade",
    "Option2": "Gatorade",
    "Option3": "Monster Energy",
    "Option4": "Red Bull",
    "Answer": "Gatorade"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 84,
    "Question": "What is the primary product of the brand Levi's?",
    "Option1": "Sneakers",
    "Option2": "Watches",
    "Option3": "Jeans",
    "Option4": "T-shirts",
    "Answer": "Jeans"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 85,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 86,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'Because You're Worth It'?",
    "Option1": "Estée Lauder",
    "Option2": "L'Oréal",
    "Option3": "Mary Kay",
    "Option4": "Chanel",
    "Answer": "L'Oréal"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 87,
    "Question": "The brand of home appliances with a red dot logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "LG",
    "Option4": "Dyson",
    "Answer": "Dyson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 88,
    "Question": "What is the brand of fast-food restaurant known for its 'Whopper' sandwich?",
    "Option1": "McDonald's",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "Burger King",
    "Option4": "Taco Bell",
    "Answer": "Burger King"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 89,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the popular Oreo cookie is:",
    "Option1": "Nabisco",
    "Option2": "Keebler",
    "Option3": "General Mills",
    "Option4": "Kraft Heinz",
    "Answer": "Nabisco"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 90,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its iconic trench coats and check pattern?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 91,
    "Question": "The car company with the 'T' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Toyota",
    "Option2": "Tesla",
    "Option3": "Ford",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Tesla"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 92,
    "Question": "What is the brand of luxury watch known for its 'Oyster' case and 'Submariner' model?",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Rolex",
    "Option3": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option4": "Breitling",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 93,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a blue bird as its logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Twitter (now X)",
    "Option4": "LinkedIn",
    "Answer": "Twitter (now X)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 94,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Flying B' logo and luxury cars?",
    "Option1": "Rolls-Royce",
    "Option2": "Bentley",
    "Option3": "Jaguar",
    "Option4": "Aston Martin",
    "Answer": "Bentley"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 95,
    "Question": "What brand of soda is known for its slogan 'The Uncola'?",
    "Option1": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option2": "Pepsi",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Sprite",
    "Answer": "7 Up"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 96,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its red-soled shoes?",
    "Option1": "Jimmy Choo",
    "Option2": "Manolo Blahnik",
    "Option3": "Christian Louboutin",
    "Option4": "Salvatore Ferragamo",
    "Answer": "Christian Louboutin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 97,
    "Question": "The brand of high-end handbags with an iconic 'monogram' pattern is:",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Hermès",
    "Option3": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 98,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its slogan 'Open Happiness'?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "Sprite",
    "Option4": "7 Up",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 99,
    "Question": "The car company that produces the F-150 and Mustang models is:",
    "Option1": "Chevrolet",
    "Option2": "Ford",
    "Option3": "Dodge",
    "Option4": "Toyota",
    "Answer": "Ford"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 100,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its search engine and the 'Don't be evil' motto?",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Apple",
    "Option3": "Google",
    "Option4": "Amazon",
    "Answer": "Google"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 101,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Jumpman' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Adidas",
    "Option3": "Jordan Brand",
    "Option4": "Puma",
    "Answer": "Jordan Brand"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 102,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its iconic 'Swiss Army Knife'?",
    "Option1": "Leatherman",
    "Option2": "Wenger",
    "Option3": "Victorinox",
    "Option4": "Gerber",
    "Answer": "Victorinox"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 103,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a ghost logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Snapchat",
    "Option4": "TikTok",
    "Answer": "Snapchat"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 104,
    "Question": "Which brand of toys is famous for its 'Barbie' doll?",
    "Option1": "Hasbro",
    "Option2": "LEGO",
    "Option3": "Mattel",
    "Option4": "Fisher-Price",
    "Answer": "Mattel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 105,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 106,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of whiskey known for its red label?",
    "Option1": "Jack Daniel's",
    "Option2": "Jim Beam",
    "Option3": "Johnnie Walker",
    "Option4": "Maker's Mark",
    "Answer": "Johnnie Walker"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 107,
    "Question": "The brand of camera known for its iconic 'Eos' series is:",
    "Option1": "Nikon",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "Canon",
    "Option4": "Fujifilm",
    "Answer": "Canon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 108,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'I'm Lovin' It'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 109,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Three-Stripes' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Adidas",
    "Option4": "Under Armour",
    "Answer": "Adidas"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 110,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic 'Check' pattern and trench coats?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 111,
    "Question": "The brand of chocolate known for its triangular shape is:",
    "Option1": "Cadbury",
    "Option2": "Hershey's",
    "Option3": "Toblerone",
    "Option4": "Lindt",
    "Answer": "Toblerone"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 112,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Golden Arches' logo?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "McDonald's",
    "Option4": "KFC",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 113,
    "Question": "The brand of energy drink known for its bull logo is:",
    "Option1": "Monster Energy",
    "Option2": "Red Bull",
    "Option3": "Rockstar",
    "Option4": "NOS Energy Drink",
    "Answer": "Red Bull"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 114,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its 'Just Do It' slogan?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 115,
    "Question": "The brand of luxury car with a four-ring logo is:",
    "Option1": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option2": "BMW",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Lexus",
    "Answer": "Audi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 116,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its 'swoosh' logo?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 117,
    "Question": "The brand of home furnishing known for its flat-pack furniture is:",
    "Option1": "Walmart",
    "Option2": "Target",
    "Option3": "IKEA",
    "Option4": "The Home Depot",
    "Answer": "IKEA"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 118,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of soft drink known for its red and white logo?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Dr Pepper",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 119,
    "Question": "The brand of technology company with a bitten apple logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Apple",
    "Option4": "Google",
    "Answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 120,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'golden arches' and 'Happy Meal'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 121,
    "Question": "The brand of watches known for its crown logo is:",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option3": "Rolex",
    "Option4": "TAG Heuer",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 122,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic fragrance 'Chanel No. 5'?",
    "Option1": "Dior",
    "Option2": "Gucci",
    "Option3": "Chanel",
    "Option4": "Hermès",
    "Answer": "Chanel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 123,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the PlayStation gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Nintendo",
    "Option3": "Sony",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Sony"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 124,
    "Question": "Which car company has a star-shaped logo and is headquartered in Germany?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Mercedes-Benz"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 125,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its online marketplace and its Kindle e-readers?",
    "Option1": "eBay",
    "Option2": "Walmart",
    "Option3": "Amazon",
    "Option4": "Alibaba",
    "Answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 126,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the Xbox gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Sony",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Nintendo",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Microsoft"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 127,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its slogan 'The Ultimate Driving Machine'?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Audi",
    "Option3": "Toyota",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "BMW"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 128,
    "Question": "The brand of sports drink known for its lightning bolt logo is:",
    "Option1": "Powerade",
    "Option2": "Gatorade",
    "Option3": "Monster Energy",
    "Option4": "Red Bull",
    "Answer": "Gatorade"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 129,
    "Question": "What is the primary product of the brand Levi's?",
    "Option1": "Sneakers",
    "Option2": "Watches",
    "Option3": "Jeans",
    "Option4": "T-shirts",
    "Answer": "Jeans"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 130,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 131,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'Because You're Worth It'?",
    "Option1": "Estée Lauder",
    "Option2": "L'Oréal",
    "Option3": "Mary Kay",
    "Option4": "Chanel",
    "Answer": "L'Oréal"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 132,
    "Question": "The brand of home appliances with a red dot logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "LG",
    "Option4": "Dyson",
    "Answer": "Dyson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 133,
    "Question": "What is the brand of fast-food restaurant known for its 'Whopper' sandwich?",
    "Option1": "McDonald's",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "Burger King",
    "Option4": "Taco Bell",
    "Answer": "Burger King"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 134,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the popular Oreo cookie is:",
    "Option1": "Nabisco",
    "Option2": "Keebler",
    "Option3": "General Mills",
    "Option4": "Kraft Heinz",
    "Answer": "Nabisco"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 135,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its iconic trench coats and check pattern?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 136,
    "Question": "The car company with the 'T' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Toyota",
    "Option2": "Tesla",
    "Option3": "Ford",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Tesla"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 137,
    "Question": "What is the brand of luxury watch known for its 'Oyster' case and 'Submariner' model?",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Rolex",
    "Option3": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option4": "Breitling",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 138,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a blue bird as its logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Twitter (now X)",
    "Option4": "LinkedIn",
    "Answer": "Twitter (now X)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 139,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Flying B' logo and luxury cars?",
    "Option1": "Rolls-Royce",
    "Option2": "Bentley",
    "Option3": "Jaguar",
    "Option4": "Aston Martin",
    "Answer": "Bentley"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 140,
    "Question": "What brand of soda is known for its slogan 'The Uncola'?",
    "Option1": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option2": "Pepsi",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Sprite",
    "Answer": "7 Up"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 141,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its red-soled shoes?",
    "Option1": "Jimmy Choo",
    "Option2": "Manolo Blahnik",
    "Option3": "Christian Louboutin",
    "Option4": "Salvatore Ferragamo",
    "Answer": "Christian Louboutin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 142,
    "Question": "The brand of high-end handbags with an iconic 'monogram' pattern is:",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Hermès",
    "Option3": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 143,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its slogan 'Open Happiness'?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "Sprite",
    "Option4": "7 Up",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 144,
    "Question": "The car company that produces the F-150 and Mustang models is:",
    "Option1": "Chevrolet",
    "Option2": "Ford",
    "Option3": "Dodge",
    "Option4": "Toyota",
    "Answer": "Ford"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 145,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its search engine and the 'Don't be evil' motto?",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Apple",
    "Option3": "Google",
    "Option4": "Amazon",
    "Answer": "Google"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 146,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Jumpman' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Adidas",
    "Option3": "Jordan Brand",
    "Option4": "Puma",
    "Answer": "Jordan Brand"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 147,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its iconic 'Swiss Army Knife'?",
    "Option1": "Leatherman",
    "Option2": "Wenger",
    "Option3": "Victorinox",
    "Option4": "Gerber",
    "Answer": "Victorinox"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 148,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a ghost logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Snapchat",
    "Option4": "TikTok",
    "Answer": "Snapchat"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 149,
    "Question": "Which brand of toys is famous for its 'Barbie' doll?",
    "Option1": "Hasbro",
    "Option2": "LEGO",
    "Option3": "Mattel",
    "Option4": "Fisher-Price",
    "Answer": "Mattel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 150,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 151,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of whiskey known for its red label?",
    "Option1": "Jack Daniel's",
    "Option2": "Jim Beam",
    "Option3": "Johnnie Walker",
    "Option4": "Maker's Mark",
    "Answer": "Johnnie Walker"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 152,
    "Question": "The brand of camera known for its iconic 'Eos' series is:",
    "Option1": "Nikon",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "Canon",
    "Option4": "Fujifilm",
    "Answer": "Canon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 153,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'I'm Lovin' It'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 154,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Three-Stripes' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Adidas",
    "Option4": "Under Armour",
    "Answer": "Adidas"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 155,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic 'Check' pattern and trench coats?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 156,
    "Question": "The brand of chocolate known for its triangular shape is:",
    "Option1": "Cadbury",
    "Option2": "Hershey's",
    "Option3": "Toblerone",
    "Option4": "Lindt",
    "Answer": "Toblerone"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 157,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Golden Arches' logo?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "McDonald's",
    "Option4": "KFC",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 158,
    "Question": "The brand of energy drink known for its bull logo is:",
    "Option1": "Monster Energy",
    "Option2": "Red Bull",
    "Option3": "Rockstar",
    "Option4": "NOS Energy Drink",
    "Answer": "Red Bull"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 159,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its 'Just Do It' slogan?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 160,
    "Question": "The brand of luxury car with a four-ring logo is:",
    "Option1": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option2": "BMW",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Lexus",
    "Answer": "Audi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 161,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its 'swoosh' logo?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 162,
    "Question": "The brand of home furnishing known for its flat-pack furniture is:",
    "Option1": "Walmart",
    "Option2": "Target",
    "Option3": "IKEA",
    "Option4": "The Home Depot",
    "Answer": "IKEA"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 163,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of soft drink known for its red and white logo?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Dr Pepper",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no. 164": "The brand of technology company with a bitten apple logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Apple",
    "Option4": "Google",
    "Answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 165,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'golden arches' and 'Happy Meal'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 166,
    "Question": "The brand of watches known for its crown logo is:",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option3": "Rolex",
    "Option4": "TAG Heuer",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 167,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic fragrance 'Chanel No. 5'?",
    "Option1": "Dior",
    "Option2": "Gucci",
    "Option3": "Chanel",
    "Option4": "Hermès",
    "Answer": "Chanel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 168,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the PlayStation gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Nintendo",
    "Option3": "Sony",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Sony"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 169,
    "Question": "Which car company has a star-shaped logo and is headquartered in Germany?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Mercedes-Benz"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 170,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its online marketplace and its Kindle e-readers?",
    "Option1": "eBay",
    "Option2": "Walmart",
    "Option3": "Amazon",
    "Option4": "Alibaba",
    "Answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 171,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the Xbox gaming console is:",
    "Option1": "Sony",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Nintendo",
    "Option4": "Sega",
    "Answer": "Microsoft"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 172,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its slogan 'The Ultimate Driving Machine'?",
    "Option1": "BMW",
    "Option2": "Audi",
    "Option3": "Toyota",
    "Option4": "Ford",
    "Answer": "BMW"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 173,
    "Question": "The brand of sports drink known for its lightning bolt logo is:",
    "Option1": "Powerade",
    "Option2": "Gatorade",
    "Option3": "Monster Energy",
    "Option4": "Red Bull",
    "Answer": "Gatorade"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 174,
    "Question": "What is the primary product of the brand Levi's?",
    "Option1": "Sneakers",
    "Option2": "Watches",
    "Option3": "Jeans",
    "Option4": "T-shirts",
    "Answer": "Jeans"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 175,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 176,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'Because You're Worth It'?",
    "Option1": "Estée Lauder",
    "Option2": "L'Oréal",
    "Option3": "Mary Kay",
    "Option4": "Chanel",
    "Answer": "L'Oréal"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 177,
    "Question": "The brand of home appliances with a red dot logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "LG",
    "Option4": "Dyson",
    "Answer": "Dyson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 178,
    "Question": "What is the brand of fast-food restaurant known for its 'Whopper' sandwich?",
    "Option1": "McDonald's",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "Burger King",
    "Option4": "Taco Bell",
    "Answer": "Burger King"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 179,
    "Question": "The brand that produces the popular Oreo cookie is:",
    "Option1": "Nabisco",
    "Option2": "Keebler",
    "Option3": "General Mills",
    "Option4": "Kraft Heinz",
    "Answer": "Nabisco"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 180,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its iconic trench coats and check pattern?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 181,
    "Question": "The car company with the 'T' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Toyota",
    "Option2": "Tesla",
    "Option3": "Ford",
    "Option4": "Volkswagen",
    "Answer": "Tesla"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 182,
    "Question": "What is the brand of luxury watch known for its 'Oyster' case and 'Submariner' model?",
    "Option1": "Omega",
    "Option2": "Rolex",
    "Option3": "Patek Philippe",
    "Option4": "Breitling",
    "Answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 183,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a blue bird as its logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Twitter (now X)",
    "Option4": "LinkedIn",
    "Answer": "Twitter (now X)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 184,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Flying B' logo and luxury cars?",
    "Option1": "Rolls-Royce",
    "Option2": "Bentley",
    "Option3": "Jaguar",
    "Option4": "Aston Martin",
    "Answer": "Bentley"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 185,
    "Question": "What brand of soda is known for its slogan 'The Uncola'?",
    "Option1": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option2": "Pepsi",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Sprite",
    "Answer": "7 Up"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 186,
    "Question": "Which brand is famous for its red-soled shoes?",
    "Option1": "Jimmy Choo",
    "Option2": "Manolo Blahnik",
    "Option3": "Christian Louboutin",
    "Option4": "Salvatore Ferragamo",
    "Answer": "Christian Louboutin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 187,
    "Question": "The brand of high-end handbags with an iconic 'monogram' pattern is:",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Hermès",
    "Option3": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 188,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its slogan 'Open Happiness'?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "Sprite",
    "Option4": "7 Up",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 189,
    "Question": "The car company that produces the F-150 and Mustang models is:",
    "Option1": "Chevrolet",
    "Option2": "Ford",
    "Option3": "Dodge",
    "Option4": "Toyota",
    "Answer": "Ford"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 190,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its search engine and the 'Don't be evil' motto?",
    "Option1": "Microsoft",
    "Option2": "Apple",
    "Option3": "Google",
    "Option4": "Amazon",
    "Answer": "Google"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 191,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Jumpman' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Adidas",
    "Option3": "Jordan Brand",
    "Option4": "Puma",
    "Answer": "Jordan Brand"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 192,
    "Question": "What brand is known for its iconic 'Swiss Army Knife'?",
    "Option1": "Leatherman",
    "Option2": "Wenger",
    "Option3": "Victorinox",
    "Option4": "Gerber",
    "Answer": "Victorinox"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 193,
    "Question": "The social media platform with a ghost logo is:",
    "Option1": "Facebook",
    "Option2": "Instagram",
    "Option3": "Snapchat",
    "Option4": "TikTok",
    "Answer": "Snapchat"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 194,
    "Question": "Which brand of toys is famous for its 'Barbie' doll?",
    "Option1": "Hasbro",
    "Option2": "LEGO",
    "Option3": "Mattel",
    "Option4": "Fisher-Price",
    "Answer": "Mattel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 195,
    "Question": "The brand of coffee known for its 'red cup' in the holiday season is:",
    "Option1": "Dunkin' Donuts",
    "Option2": "Starbucks",
    "Option3": "Peet's Coffee",
    "Option4": "Costa Coffee",
    "Answer": "Starbucks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 196,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of whiskey known for its red label?",
    "Option1": "Jack Daniel's",
    "Option2": "Jim Beam",
    "Option3": "Johnnie Walker",
    "Option4": "Maker's Mark",
    "Answer": "Johnnie Walker"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 197,
    "Question": "The brand of camera known for its iconic 'Eos' series is:",
    "Option1": "Nikon",
    "Option2": "Sony",
    "Option3": "Canon",
    "Option4": "Fujifilm",
    "Answer": "Canon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 198,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its slogan 'I'm Lovin' It'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 199,
    "Question": "The brand of sportswear known for its 'Three-Stripes' logo is:",
    "Option1": "Nike",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Adidas",
    "Option4": "Under Armour",
    "Answer": "Adidas"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 200,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its iconic 'Check' pattern and trench coats?",
    "Option1": "Gucci",
    "Option2": "Louis Vuitton",
    "Option3": "Burberry",
    "Option4": "Prada",
    "Answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 201,
    "Question": "The brand of chocolate known for its triangular shape is:",
    "Option1": "Cadbury",
    "Option2": "Hershey's",
    "Option3": "Toblerone",
    "Option4": "Lindt",
    "Answer": "Toblerone"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 202,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'Golden Arches' logo?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "McDonald's",
    "Option4": "KFC",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 203,
    "Question": "The brand of energy drink known for its bull logo is:",
    "Option1": "Monster Energy",
    "Option2": "Red Bull",
    "Option3": "Rockstar",
    "Option4": "NOS Energy Drink",
    "Answer": "Red Bull"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 204,
    "Question": "What brand is famous for its 'Just Do It' slogan?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 205,
    "Question": "The brand of luxury car with a four-ring logo is:",
    "Option1": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "Option2": "BMW",
    "Option3": "Audi",
    "Option4": "Lexus",
    "Answer": "Audi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 206,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its 'swoosh' logo?",
    "Option1": "Adidas",
    "Option2": "Puma",
    "Option3": "Nike",
    "Option4": "Reebok",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 207,
    "Question": "The brand of home furnishing known for its flat-pack furniture is:",
    "Option1": "Walmart",
    "Option2": "Target",
    "Option3": "IKEA",
    "Option4": "The Home Depot",
    "Answer": "IKEA"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 208,
    "Question": "What is the global brand of soft drink known for its red and white logo?",
    "Option1": "Pepsi",
    "Option2": "Coca-Cola",
    "Option3": "7 Up",
    "Option4": "Dr Pepper",
    "Answer": "Coca-Cola"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 209,
    "Question": "The brand of technology company with a bitten apple logo is:",
    "Option1": "Samsung",
    "Option2": "Microsoft",
    "Option3": "Apple",
    "Option4": "Google",
    "Answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 210,
    "Question": "Which brand is known for its iconic 'golden arches' and 'Happy Meal'?",
    "Option1": "Burger King",
    "Option2": "Wendy's",
    "Option3": "KFC",
    "Option4": "McDonald's",
    "Answer": "McDonald's"
  }
]